research that says
that the average
American has fewer
friends now than
they did 15
years ago.
Yeah. And I
was so interested
in that because
it seems like
if we want
to get to
a world where
there's more human
connection- Mm-hmm this
is the trend
that we're going
to have to
grapple with. Yeah.
just to give
some data on
this, in the
American Time Use
Survey, over the
last 20 years,
the amount of
time American adults
spend socializing in
person has
dropped by
nearly 30%.
For ages 15
to 24, according
to the surgeon
general, it's nearly
70%.
And I look
at that data
and I think
to myself, well,
maybe if we're
all socializing digitally,
that doesn't
matter so much.
Maybe there's a
future where that's
actually fine.
But there's also
data that suggests
that we're
struggling somewhat.
The number of
Americans who say
that they don't
have a single
close friend- Yeah
that share has
jumped- Yeah, it's
really sad from
3% to 12%
in the last
30 years. It
feels to me
like with all
the tools that
we've built for
human connection, we're
struggling to connect.